Guide to the Neal Lane papers, 1998-2001, MS 502 MS 502
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Cabinet Files, 1998-2001; Files relating to the Office of Science and Technology Policy (OSTP) and the National Science Foundation. Memoranda, meeting materials, agendas, reports and notes relating to the various divisions of the OSTP: Environment, Science, Technology and National Secur
  - Sub-Series K: Subject Files: Department of Energy, OSTP, National Science Foundation, foreign travel files, "name files," relating to meetings and correspondence, and other
    - Federal Demonstration Partnership, 1995-1997 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Federal High Performance Computing Program, 1988, 1989, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Funding, R (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - NSF and G-7 countires meeting and other materials, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Government Performance and Results Act (GPRA), 1997 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Government shutdown, 1995 September - December (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Human Capital Initiative, 1992-1997 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    - Inspector General, correspondence, Investigation Report, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Japan, 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - "Knowledge and Distributed Intelligence (KDI)," 1996-1998 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Mars, "Life on Mars," 1996-1998 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Math and Physical Sciences, 1995, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Mexico, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - National Institute for the Environment (NIE), 1995-1998 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST), 1994 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - National Research Council, "A Dialogue on Research University Futures," 1997 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - National Science and Technology Council, Antarctic, 1996 April (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - National Science Foundation, budget and planning document, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - National Science Board, FY 99, Budget Long Range (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - National Science Board (NSB), Long Range and Strategic Planning, 1997 November 14 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - National Science Board, Long Range and Strategic Planning, 1998 February (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - National Science Board, Budget and Long Range Planning, 1998 May 7 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - National Science Board, 345th Meeting, minutes, University of Houston, Texas, 1997 October 8-9 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - NSB, Executive Committee meeting, 1998 May 6 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Next Generation Internet, 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Physics Roundtable, 1992-1995 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Polar issues, 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - President's Management Council, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Publications:
    - The AEI Press Catalog of Books, Fall/Winter 1993-1994 (Box 42)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Annual Report, 1993 (Box 42)
    - AAAS, '94, Science and a Changing World (Box 42)
    - American Institute of Physics, Report, 1988-1989 (Box 42)
    - American Society for Engineering Education, 1994 (Box 42)
    - Arctic Research of the United States, Fall 1993, Spring 1994 (Box 42)
    - Biotechnology for the 21st Century, 1992-1994 (Box 42)
    - Biotechnology Opportunities: The NSF Role, 1991 April 10 (Box 42)
    - Carnegie Quarterly, Fall 1994-Winter 1995 (Box 42)
    - The Chinese Academy of Sciences, [1989] (Box 42)
    - Chinese Biodiversity, 1998 August (Box 42)
    - Consequences: The Nature Implications of Environmental Chang, 1995-1996 (Box 42)
    - FCCSET Initiatives in the FY 1994 Budget, 1993 April 8 (Box 43)
    - Federal Funding for Environmental R (Box 43)
    - The Federal Investment in Science, Mathematics, Engineering, and Technology Education: Where Now? What Next?, 1993 June (Box 43)
    - Federally Funded Genome Research: Science and Technology Transfer Issues, Proceedings of a Public Meeting, 1992 May 21 (Box 43)
    - Global Change Research Program: A component of the U.S. Global Change Research Program, Research Opportunities, 1993 (Box 43)
    - Government-University-Industry Research Roundtable, 1989-1993, 1997 (Box 43)
    - In the National Interest: The Federal Government and Research-Intensive Universities, 1992 December (Box 43)
    - Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, 1995-1996 (Box 43)
    - Investing in Human Potential: Science and Engineering at the Crossroads, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Lamont-Doherty Earth Observatory, 1993 (Box 43)
    - Lamont Log, 1993 Autumn (Box 43)
    - Lamont-Doherty Geological Observatory, report, 1990-1991 (Box 43)
    - The Liberal Art of Science: Agenda for Action, 1990 (Box 43)
    - A Long-range Plan for the Multinational Coordinated Arabidopsis thaliana Genome Research Project, undated (Box 43)
    - A National Computing Initiative: The Agenda for Leadership, 1987 (Box 43)
    - Our Changing Planet: A Report by the Committee on Earth and Environmental Sciences of the Federal Coordinating Council for Science, Engineering and Technology, 1994-1997 (Box 43)
    - Pathways to Excellence: A Federal Strategy for Science, Mathematics, Engineering, and Technology Education, 1993 (Box 43)
    - Preventing Contemporary Intergroup Violence, Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1993 (Box 43)
    - Project 2061, American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1989, 1991, 1993 (Box 43)
    - Projects in Scientific Computing, Pittsburgh Supercomputing Center, 1993 (Box 43)
    - Report of the Genome Patent Working Group to the Committee on Life Sciences and Health, 1992 July 29 (Box 43)
    - Resource Guide to Selected Undergraduate Programs of 10 Federal Agencies, 1993-1994 (Box 43)
    - Science and Technology in U.S. International Affairs, 1992 January (Box 43)
    - Science, Technology, and Government for a Changing World,, 1993 April (Box 43)
    - Science, Technology, and the States in America's Third Century, 1992 September (Box 43)
    - Spectra: The Newsletter of the Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1994-1995 (Box 43)
    - Trends in the Structure of Federal Science Support, 1992 December (Box 43)
    - R (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Radio Spectrum, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - RaDiUS, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - "A Report on Science Technology in the Clinton Administration: recommendations for transition planning," 1992 November (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Research facilities, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Science, articles, clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Science and Technology, Clinton Administration, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Science in the National Interest, 1994 Forum (Box 43, Folder 8-9)
    - Semiconductor Technology Council, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Sigma Xi: Scientific Research Society, 1990-2000 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Smithsonian, "How We Discover: A Collaboration Exhibit and Educational Outreach Program of the National Science Foundation and the Smithsonian Institution," 1996-1998 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - State/Federal Technology Partnership (SFTP), 1996 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Statewide Systemic Initiatives Program, 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Symposium on the Underclass, 1992 April 24 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Technology, background material, articles, reports, clippings, "Council on Competitiveness," 1987-1993 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Third International Math and Science Study (TIMSS), 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 7-8)
    - Universities, Academic research, articles, clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Universities, Higher Education, general articles, notes, clippings, 1986-1993 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (UCAR), 1997 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - White Paper on Science and Technology Policy Issues, 1998 April (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - "Year of the Ocean," National Research Council, Ocean Studies Board, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous notes, correspondence, National Science Foundation, 1995-1997 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Rice University research publication reprints, offprints, theses, group research, lectures, other research material, 1968-
    - Articles, reprints, 1968-1980 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Reprints of Articles Since 1987 and Preprints of Articles Submitted for Publication, "Atomic and Molecular Sciences," 1987-1989 (Box 44, Folder 16-18)
    - Article reprints, 1988-1994 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - "Heavy-Particle Atomic Collisions," Lectures for Los Alamos National Laboratory Summer School on Atomic and Molecular Physics, 1990 July (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Department of Energy (DOE) grant, "Theoretical Atomic Collision Physics,"1995 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Welch Foundation, 1992-1994 (Box 44, Folder 22-23)
    - Abstract, Division of Atomic. Molecular and Optical Physics of the American Physical Society, 1994 April (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - The Physical Review, 1962-1969 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - "Polarization and Exchange Effects in Low-Energy Electron-H2 Scattering," Ronald J.W. Henry, Neal Lane, Physical Review, 1969 July 5 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - "Collisional excitation of He+ ions by carbon atoms," R.E. Yager, Neal Lane, J. Phys. B, 1969 July 14 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - "Differential Elastic and Rotational Excitation Cross Sections for Electron-H² Scattering," Neal Lane, S. Geltman, Physical Review, 1969 August 5 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - "Total and Excitation-Transfer Cross Sections for Collisions between 2³ S Metastable and Ground-State Helium Atoms," S.A. Evans, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review, 1969 December 5 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - "Localized Excited States of Helium in Liquid Helium," A.P. Hickman, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review Letters, 1971 May 17 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - "Low-Energy and Fine Structure Excitation Scattering of Ground-State C+ Ions by Hydrogen," Jon C. Weisheit, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1971 July (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - "Calculation of Cross Sections for Penning Ionization: He*(2¹S,2³S) + H (1²S)," J.S. Cohen, N.F. Lane, Chemical Physics Letters, 1971 September 1 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - "Low Energy Electron-Molecule Scattering Experiments and the Theory of Rotational Excitation," D.E. Golden, Neal F. Lane, A. Temkin, E. Gerjuoy, Reviews of Modern Physics, 1971 October (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - "Quantum-Mechanical Calculation of Cross Sections for Inelastic Atom-Atom Collisions. I. Inelastic 2³ S — 2³ P Collisions between Metastable and Ground-State Helium Atoms," S.A. Evans, J.S. Cohen, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1971 December (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - "Calculation of cross sections for chemiionization of H by He (2¹S) and He (2³S) metastable atoms," J.S. Cohen, Neal F. Lane, J. Physics B, 1973 May (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - "Quantum-Mechanical Calculation of Inelastic Cross Sections for 1 ¹S — 2 ³S Excitation Collisions of Ground-State He Atoms with He+ Ions," S.A. Evans, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1973 September (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - "Theoretical Description of Pressure Shifts and Quenching of Excited Atomic States in Liguid Helium," W, Streets, A.P. Hickman, N.F. Lane, Chemical Physics Letters, 1974 September 1 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - "The Fredhold Method in Low Energy Electron-Molecule Scattering: Static Exchange," Thomas G. Winter, Neal F. Lane, Chemical Physics Letters, 1975 February 1 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - "Interactions of excited (n=3) and ground-state helium atoms: Potential curves and inelastic processes," W.J. Steets, N.F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1975 June (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - "Rotational excitation of HF in slow collisions with He," Lee A. Collins, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1975 September (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - "Nature of excited helium atoms in liquid helium: A theoretical model," A.P. Hickman, W. Steets, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review B, 1975 November 1 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - "Pseudo-bound-state study of low-energy electron-molecule collisions: Elastic e-H2 scattering," Michael A. Morrison, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1975 December (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - "Theoretical Study of Low-Energy Electron-CO2 Scattering," Michael A. Morrison, Lee A. Collins, Neal F. Lane, Chemical Physics Letters, 1976 September 1 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - "Quantum-mechanical calculations of rotational-excitation cross sections for HCI, DCI, DF, and HF in slow collisions with He," L.A. Collins, N.F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1976 October (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - "He(2³S) bubble in liquid helium," J. Wisdon, T.W. Hartquist, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review B, 1976 November 1 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - "Chemiionization of the hydrogen molecule by He(2³S) and He(2¹S) atoms: potential surfaces, autoionizationi widths, and cross sections," James S. Cohen, Neal F. Lane, The Journal of Chemical Physics, 1977 January (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - "Low-energy electron-molecule scattering: Application of coupled-channel theory to e-CO2 collisions," Michael A. Morrison, Neal F. Lane, Lee A. Collins, Physical Review A, 1977 June (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - "A Theoretical Calculation of Cross Sections for Rotational Excitation in e - CO2 Scattering," Michael A. Morrison, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A: General Physics, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - "Exact eigenvalues, electronic wavefunctions and their derivatives with respect to the internuclear separation from the lowest 20 states of the HeH²+ molecule," T.G. Winter, M.D. Duncan, N.F. Lane, J. Physics B, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - "Cluster Approach to a Single Hydrogen Atom in a Nickel Crystal," R.W. Simpson, N.F. Lane, R.C. Chaney, Journal of Nuclear Materials, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - "Electron transfer in collisions of He++ions with H atoms at 4 He++impact erergies of 0.1-20.0 keV," Thomas G. Winter, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1978 January (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - "Theory of in inelastic collisions between low-lying excited-and ground-state Ne atoms," James S. Cohen, Lee A. Collins, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1978 April (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - "Ab initio LCAO-MO Cluster-Type Calculation of the Self-Consistent Electronic Screening Charge Density Around a Single Hydrogen Impurity in a Nickel Crystal," R.W. Simpson, N.F. Lane, R.C. Chaney, International Journal of Quantum Chemistry, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - "The State of Theory," Neal Lane, George J. Schulz Memorial Symposium, 1979 Summer (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - "Threshold Structure in the Vibrational Excitation of CO2 by Low-Energy Electrons," Michael Morrison, Neal F. Lane, Chemical Physics Letters, 1979 October 15 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - "Atomic excitations in He+ and H+ reflection from a metal surface," L.W. Carlson, N.F. Lane, J. Phys. B, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - "Charge transfer for He²+ on H using molecular bases with pland-wave translational factors," G.J. Hatton, N.F. Lane, T.G. Winters, J. Physics B, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - "Molecular-state treatment of collisions between protons and He+ ions," Thomas G. Winter, Gregory J. Hatton, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1980 September (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - "Inelastic electron-ion scattering in a dense plasma," G.J. Hatton, N.F. Lane, J.C. Weisheit, J. Phys. B, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 35)
    - "Radiative charge transfer in collisions of He²+ ions and ground-state H atoms," B.W. West, Neal F. Lane, James S. Cohen, Physical Review A, 1982 December (Box 45, Folder 36)
    - "Near-threshold vibrational excitation in electron-CO2 collisions: A simple model," Barbara L. Whitten, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1982 December (Box 45, Folder 37)
    - "Nonadjustable exchange-correlation model for electron scattering from closed-shell atoms and molecules," J.K. O'Connell, N.F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1983 April (Box 45, Folder 38)
    - "Overview of Electron-Molecule Collision Processes," Neal F. Lane, Verlag Chemie International, Inc., 1983 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - "Plasma-screening effects on electron-impact excitation of hydrogenic ions in dense plasmas," B.L. Whitten, N.F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1984 February (Box 45, Folder 40)
    - "Fundamental Advances in the Theory of Electron-Molecule Collisions," Neal F. Lane, Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - "Theoretical calculation of Penning-ionization cross sections for collisions of He(2¹'³ S) with sodium atoms, James S. Cohen, Richard L. Martin, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1985 January (Box 45, Folder 42)
    - "Molecular-state treatment of excitation and charge-transfer processes in H+ +He (1 s²) collisions, M. Kimura, Physical Review A, 1985 April (Box 45, Folder 43)
    - "Evolution of electronic probability density in a-H collisions, Thomas G. Winter, Chizuko M. Dutta, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1985 April (Box 45, Folder 44)
    - "R-matrix approach to electron transfer in a-H collisions, Thomas G. winter, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1985 April (Box 45, Folder 45)
    - "Charge transfer in ion-molecule collisions at keV energy regime: Study of H+ +H2 collisions by electron-translation-factor-modified molecular-orbital-expansion method," M. Kimura, Physical Review A, 1985 August (Box 45, Folder 46)
    - "Unified treatment of slow atom-atom and ion-atom collisions. II. Applications to H+ +H and C6+ + H collisions," M. Kimura, C.D. Lin, Physical Review A, 1985 September (Box 45, Folder 47)
    - "Li(2s--2p) and Na(3s--3p) excitation in Li-Na collisions," M. Kimura, R.E. Olson, J. Phys. B, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 48)
    - "Classical study of the collision of a highly excited atom with the molecules HF and HCI," S. Preston, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1986 January (Box 45, Folder 49)
    - "Electron capture in Ar+ +H2 collisions in the keV energy regime," M. Kimura, S. Chapman, N. Lane, Physical Review A, 1986 March (Box 45, Folder 50)
    - "Theoretical Study of Alignment and Orientation in Li+ + He Collisions," M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, Physical Review Letters, 1986 May 19 (Box 45, Folder 51)
    - "Theoretical investigation of charge transfer in collisions of C6+ and N7+ ions with H and H2 targets at low to intermediate energy," M. Kimura, Physical Review A, 1986 June (Box 45, Folder 52)
    - "Charge transfer and excitation processes in p-He collisions studied using a unified atomic-orbital-molecular-orbital matching method," M. Kimura, C.D. Lin, Physical Review A, 1986 July (Box 45, Folder 53)
    - "Symmetric resonant charge transfer in H+ +H and He²+ + He collisions at extremely low energies," M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1986 November (Box 45, Folder 54-55)
    - "Theoretical Studies of Rydberg-Neutral Collisions: Classical and Quantum Mechanical Treatments," Neal Lane, Oji International Seminar on Highly Excited States of Atoms and Molecules, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 56)
    - "Differential Cross Sections for Electron Capture in Highly Charged Ion Collisions with He and H2 in the keV Regime," M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, [1986] (Box 45, Folder 57)
    - "Density matrices of the n=2 and n=3 Manifolds of Excited H Atoms Formed in p-H Collisions at 1-50 keV Impact Energies," Ashok Jain, C.D. Lin, W. Fritsch, [1986] (Box 45, Folder 58)
    - "Semiclassical Study of the Collision of a Highly Excited Rydberg Atom with the Molecules HF and HCI," M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, [1986] (Box 45, Folder 59)
    - "Theoretical Treatment of Electron Capture and Excitation in Two-Electron System Ion-Atom, Atom-Atom Collisions at Low to Initermediate Energy," M. Kimura, Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 60)
    - "An Overview of Low-Energy Ion-Atom Collisions," C.D. Lin, W. Fritsch, M. Kimura, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 61)
    - "Traveling-molecular-orbital-expansion studies of electron capture in collisions of fully stripped ions (Z=6-9) with H and H2," M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1987 January 1 (Box 45, Folder 62)
    - "Plasma screening effects on proton-impact excitation of positive ions," K. Scheibner, J.C. Weisheit, N.F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1987 February 1 (Box 45, Folder 63)
    - "Differential cross sections for electron transfer and elastic scattering in collisions between a particles and hydrogen atoms," Thomas G. Winter, Gregory J. Hatton, Amy R. Day, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1987 July 15 (Box 45, Folder 64)
    - "Role of atomic resonances in the ionization of potassium atoms in slow collisions with He (2¹'³ S)," Karl F. Scheibner, James S. Cohen, Richard L. Martin, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1987 September 15 (Box 45, Folder 65)
    - "State changing in collisions of Rb(ns) Rydberg atoms with HF," A. Kalamarides, L.N. Goeller, K.A. Smith, F.B. Dunning, M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1987 October 1 (Box 45, Folder 66)
    - "Theory of Ion-Surface Collisions: Case Study of He+ Projectile Ion on TaC Surface," Mineo Kimura, Neal F. Lane, Kazumi Fujima, Hiroshi Sato, Nuclear Instruments and Methods in Physics Research, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 67)
    - "A Unified Atomic-Orbital and Molecular-Orbital Matching Method for Ion-Atom and Atom-Atom Collisions," M. Kimura, C.D. Lin, Comments At. Mol. Phys., 1987 (Box 45, Folder 68)
    - "Coherence study of Li (3²D) excitation in 2.5-15.0 keV Li+-He collisions," T. Andersen, H-P Neitzke, M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, J. Phys. B, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 69)
    - "Coherence study of Li (3²D) excitation in 2.5-15.0 keV Li+-He collisions," T. Andersen, H-P Neitzke, M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, J. Phys. B, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 70)
    - "Alignment and orientation of the excited h(2 p) orbital following H+He collisions at intermediate energies," M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1988 April 15 (Box 45, Folder 71)
    - "Alexander Dalgarno Contributions to Atomic and Molecular Physics," Neal Lane, Advances in Atomic and Molecular Physics, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 72)
    - "The Charge Transfer Collision Between a Low Energy Ion and a Solid Surface," Kazumi Fujima, Hirohiko Adachi, Mineo Kimura, Neal Lane, Nuclear Instruments and Methods in Physics Research, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 73)
    - "Current Status of Theoretical Studies in Ion-Atom Collisions at Low to Intermediate Collision Energies," M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, C.D. Lin, Chinese Journal of Physics, 1989 February (Box 45, Folder 74)
    - "Quenching of low-lying Rydberg states of Na colliding with ground-state He: A semiclassical approach," A. Kumar, N.F. Lane, M. Kimura, Physical Review A, 1989 February 1 (Box 45, Folder 75)
    - "Theoretical investigation of the hypothesized crossing between the Penning and atomic autoionizing states of He+K," N.T. Padial, Richard L. Martin, James S. Cohen, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1989 March 1 (Box 45, Folder 76-77)
    - "Theoretical Penning electron-energy distributions for alkali-metal atoms: He (2¹'³ S) collisions with sodium and potassium, N.T. Padial, James S. Cohen, Richard L. Martin, Neal F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1989 July 1 (Box 45, Folder 78-79)
    - "Radiative and nonradiative charge transfer in He++H collisions at low energy," B. Zygelman, A. Dalgarno, M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1989 September 1 (Box 45, Folder 80)
    - "Spin effects in slow (H-He)+ collisions," R. Hippler, H. Madeheim, H.O. Lutz, M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1989 September 15 (Box 45, Folder 81)
    - "Absolute differential cross sections for small-angle H+-He direct and charge-transfer scattering at keV energies," L.K. Johnson, R.S. Gao, R.G. Dixson, K.A. Smith, N.F. Lane, and R.F. Stebbings, Physical Review, 1989 October 1 (Box 45, Folder 82-83)
    - "Theoretical Study of Charge Transfer in He+ +H2 Collisions in the meV Regime," M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, [1989] (Box 45, Folder 84)
    - "Molecular State Calculations for Electron Capture by Li3+IN Li3+ -Li Collision," A. Kumar, M. Kimura, N. F. Lane, [1989] (Box 45, Folder 85)
    - "Comparative molecular-orbital and atomic-orbital study of electron transfer and excitatin in He++Na (3 s) collisions at energies of 0.05 to 20 keV/amu," W. Fritsch, M. Kimura, N.F. Lane, Physical Review A, 1990 January 1 (Box 45, Folder 86)